A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Speeches, Series 15 FA383
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller vice presidential records, Speeches, Series 15
1974-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
United States. Office of the Vice President
FA383
23 Box(es)
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
President Gerald R. Ford nominated Nelson A. Rockefeller to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon in August 1974. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 26 15
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Richard Allison (FA377)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Central Files (FA378)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, National Commission on Water Quality (FA379)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Press Releases (FA382)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
Arrangement
Alphabetical by subject.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: speeches.
Energy; Education -- United States; Environmental sciences; Environmental policy; Economic policy; Drug control; Education; Economics; Technology; International relations; Veterans -- United States; United States; Government policy; Federal government -- United States; International economic relations; Human rights; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Water conservation; Water -- Pollution; Water -- Purification; Social policy; Public policy; Social sciences; Social problems; National security -- United States; International relations -- United States; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Political science; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Public health; Prevention and health
- Abortion (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Acupuncture (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Administration (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Admiral's House (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Aging (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Agriculture (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Air Pollution (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Alcoholism (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Amnesty (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Angola (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Annual Message - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Annual Message - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Scope and Contents note
  Notes, News Clips, Correctional Services, No Fault Auto Insurance, Electrical Power, Education, Environment, Drafts I-IV of Annual Message
- Annual Message - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Drafts I-IX
- Annual Message - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Annual Message - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Final Draft
- Annual Message - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Adirondacks, Correspondence, Inspector General-Education Regionalization, State Takeover
- Annual Message - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Draft I
- Annual Message - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Arts (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Assassination Attempt (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Attica Prison Revolt (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Automobile (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Aviation (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Basic Documents (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Battery Park City (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Bentsen, Lloyd (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Bible (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Bicentennial (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Black Americans (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Bonds (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Boorstein, Daniel (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Borella, Victor (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Braun, Theodore (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Brazil (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Brennan, Peter J. (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Brydges, Earl W. (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Bunche, Ralph (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Bush, George (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Busing (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Campaign, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Campaign, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Campaign, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Campaign Speeches, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Campaign, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Campaign, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Campaign, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Campaign Finance (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Campbell (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Canada (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Connon, James (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Capital Construction (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Capital Formation (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Carey, Hugh (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Carter, Jimmy (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Central Intelligence Agency Commission (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Chafee, John H. (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Chinese Americans (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Churchill, Winston (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Cigarettes (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Cities (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Civil Rights (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Coal (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Commission on Critical Choices for Americans (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Commissions & NAR (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Commissions, New York State (Box 3, Folder 67)
- Communism (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Community Development (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Confirmation NAR (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Confirmation NAR (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Congress (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Constitutional Convention (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Consumer Price Index (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Consumes (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Cardinal Cooke (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Corbin, Sol (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Courts (Box 3, Folder 78)
- Credo (Box 3, Folder 79)
- Creedmoor: Statements (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Crime (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Cuba (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Deaf (Box 3, Folder 83)
- Debates (Box 3, Folder 84)
- Defense (Box 3, Folder 85)
- Democracy (Box 3, Folder 86)
- Detente (Box 3, Folder 87)
- Detergents (Box 3, Folder 88)
- Developing Countries (Box 3, Folder 89)
- Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 3, Folder 90)
- Dickens, Fred (Box 3, Folder 91)
- Dole, Sen. Robert (Box 3, Folder 92)
- Domestic Council (Box 3, Folder 93)
- Domestic Public Forums (Box 3, Folder 94)
- Draft Proposals (Box 3, Folder 95)
- Drugs (Box 3, Folder 96)
- Drugs: NAR Statements, Letter (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Dunham, Richard L. (Box 3, Folder 98)
- Dutch Americans (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Economy (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Education (Box 4, Folder 101)
- Egypt (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Eisenhower (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Election 1972 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Election 1973 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Election 1974 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Election 1976 (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Electoral College (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Electrical Power (Box 4, Folder 109)
- Empire State Plaza (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Energy (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Energy: Democrats Plan (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Energy Program (Economic Impact) (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Energy Embargo (Box 4, Folder 114)
- Energy Independence Authority (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Energy Program (Box 4, Folder 116)
- English Americans (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Enrollment (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Environment (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Environmental Bond Issue (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Energy Resources Financing Corporation (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Erie Canal (Box 4, Folder 122)
- Ernst, Joe (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Ethics (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Federal Election Campaign Laws (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Federal Employees (Box 4, Folder 126)
- Federalism (Box 4, Folder 127)
- Federal Spending (Box 4, Folder 128)
- "The Federalist Papers" (Box 4, Folder 129)
- Finkelstein, Jerry (Box 4, Folder 130)
- Fire Fighting (Box 4, Folder 131)
- Fleischmann Committee (Box 4, Folder 132)
- Food (Box 4, Folder 133)
- Food Stamps (Box 4, Folder 134)
- Ford, Mrs. (Box 4, Folder 135)
- Ford Speeches (Box 4, Folder 136)
- Foreign Affairs (Box 4, Folder 137)
- Foreign Aid (Box 4, Folder 138)
- Foreign Policy (Box 4, Folder 139)
- Foreign Trade (Box 4, Folder 140)
- France (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Franklin, Benjamin (Box 5, Folder 142)
- Free Enterprise (Box 5, Folder 143)
- French Americans (Box 5, Folder 144)
- Friele, Berent (Box 5, Folder 145)
- Fuel (Box 5, Folder 146)
- Future (Box 5, Folder 147)
- Garbage Strike (Box 5, Folder 148)
- Gas Rationing (Box 5, Folder 149)
- Germany (Box 5, Folder 150)
- German Americans (Box 5, Folder 151)
- Godfrey, Arthur (Box 5, Folder 152)
- Goldwater, Barry (Box 5, Folder 153)
- Government Reorganization (Box 5, Folder 154)
- Governors (Box 5, Folder 155)
- Great Britain (Box 5, Folder 156)
- Greek Americans (Box 5, Folder 157)
- Gun Control (Box 5, Folder 158)
- Handicapped (Box 5, Folder 159)
- Harlem Office Building (Box 5, Folder 160)
- Harrison, Wallace (Box 5, Folder 161)
- Hatfield, Mark O. (Box 5, Folder 162)
- Health (Box 5, Folder 163)
- HEW (Department of Health, Education and Welfare) (Box 5, Folder 164)
- Higher Education (Box 5, Folder 165)
- Highway Safety (Box 5, Folder 166)
- Hinman, George L. (Box 5, Folder 167)
- Hispanic Americans (Box 5, Folder 168)
- Hospitals (Box 5, Folder 169)
- Housing (Box 5, Folder 170)
- Housing & Community Renewal (Box 5, Folder 171)
- Humphrey, Hubert H. (Box 5, Folder 172)
- Impact Aid (Box 5, Folder 173)
- Impoundment (Box 5, Folder 174)
- IBEC (International Basic Economy Corporation) (Box 5, Folder 175)
- Industrial Revolution (Box 5, Folder 176)
- Inflation (Box 5, Folder 177)
- Irish (Box 5, Folder 178)
- Israel - NAR Statements (Box 5, Folder 179)
- Israel - Resource Material (Box 5, Folder 180)
- Jackson, Sen. Henry (Box 6, Folder 181)
- Japanese Americans (Box 6, Folder 182)
- Javits, Jacob K. (Box 6, Folder 183)
- Jobs (Box 6, Folder 184)
- Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 6, Folder 185)
- King, Martin Luther, Jr. (Box 6, Folder 186)
- Kissinger (Box 6, Folder 187)
- Knapp Commission (Box 6, Folder 188)
- Knowles, John H. (Box 6, Folder 189)
- Labor (Box 6, Folder 190)
- Latin America (Box 6, Folder 191)
- Lefkowitz, Louis J. (Box 6, Folder 192)
- Legislature, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 193)
- Levitt, Arthur (Box 6, Folder 194)
- Library of Congress (Box 6, Folder 195)
- Lincoln, Abraham (Box 6, Folder 196)
- Lindsay, John (Box 6, Folder 197)
- Local Government (Box 6, Folder 198)
- Long Island Bridge (Box 6, Folder 199)
- Long Island Railroad (Box 6, Folder 200)
- Magna Carta (Box 6, Folder 201)
- Marshall, Alton G. (Box 6, Folder 202)
- Mass Transportation (Box 6, Folder 203)
- Matthews, David (Box 6, Folder 204)
- Mayaguez (Box 6, Folder 205)
- Meany, George (Box 6, Folder 206)
- Meat (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Medicaid (Box 6, Folder 208)
- Mental Health (Box 6, Folder 209)
- Messages (Box 6, Folder 210)
- Mexican Americans (Box 6, Folder 211)
- Mid-East (Box 6, Folder 212)
- Miscellaneous Writings, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 213)
- Mondale, Vice President-elect (Box 6, Folder 214)
- Morality (Box 6, Folder 215)
- Morrow, Hugh (Box 6, Folder 216)
- Multinationals (Box 6, Folder 217)
- Nadjari, Maurice (Box 6, Folder 218)
- NASA (National Aeronautical and Space Administration) (Box 6, Folder 219)
- National Primary (Box 6, Folder 220)
- Natural Gas (Box 6, Folder 221)
- Navy (Box 6, Folder 222)
- News Media (Box 6, Folder 223)
- New York City (Box 6, Folder 224)
- New York City Charter Revision Committee (Goodman Commission) [Empty folder) (Box 6, Folder 225)
- Nixon, Richard M. (Box 6, Folder 226)
- No-Fault Insurance (Box 6, Folder 227)
- Noise Pollution (Box 6, Folder 228)
- Norwegian Americans (Box 6, Folder 229)
- Novitsky, Alex (Box 6, Folder 230)
- Nuclear Power (Box 6, Folder 231)
- Nursing Homes (Box 6, Folder 232)
- Oath of Office (Box 6, Folder 233)
- Oil (Box 6, Folder 234)
- OPEC (Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries) (Box 6, Folder 235)
- Organized Crime (Box 6, Folder 236)
- Panama (Box 7, Folder 237)
- Panama Canal (Box 7, Folder 238)
- Papers (Box 7, Folder 239)
- Pardon (Box 7, Folder 240)
- Parking (Box 7, Folder 241)
- Parks (Box 7, Folder 242)
- Parochial Aid (Box 7, Folder 243)
- Party Affiliation (Box 7, Folder 244)
- Pensions (Box 7, Folder 245)
- Public Employment Relations Board (Box 7, Folder 246)
- Personnel (Box 7, Folder 247)
- Polls (Box 7, Folder 248)
- Philanthropies (Box 7, Folder 249)
- Phillips, Kevin (Box 7, Folder 250)
- Platforms (Box 7, Folder 251)
- Pocantico Hills, New York (Box 7, Folder 252)
- Police (Box 7, Folder 253)
- Polish Americans (Box 7, Folder 254)
- Population (Box 7, Folder 255)
- Pornography (Box 7, Folder 256)
- Portugal (Box 7, Folder 257)
- Poverty (Box 7, Folder 258)
- Presidency (Box 7, Folder 259)
- Prisons (Box 7, Folder 260)
- Privacy (Box 7, Folder 261)
- Private Colleges (Box 7, Folder 262)
- Productivity (Box 7, Folder 263)
- Public Administration (Box 7, Folder 264)
- Public Employees (Box 7, Folder 265)
- Public Forums (Box 7, Folder 266)
- Puerto Rican Americans (Box 7, Folder 267)
- Quotes (Box 7, Folder 268)
- Rabin, Ambassador Yitzhak (Box 7, Folder 269)
- Randolph, Jennings (Box 7, Folder 270)
- Reagan (Box 7, Folder 271)
- Recreation (Box 7, Folder 272)
- Regulatory Reforms (Box 7, Folder 273)
- Rehabilitation (Box 7, Folder 274)
- Religions (Box 7, Folder 275)
- Rent Control (Box 7, Folder 276)
- Republican National Convention (Box 7, Folder 277)
- Republican Party (Box 7, Folder 278)
- Restaurants (Box 7, Folder 279)
- Revel, Jean-Francois (Box 7, Folder 280)
- Revenue Sharing (Box 7, Folder 281)
- Revenue Sharing Drafts (Box 7, Folder 282)
- Riots (Kerner Commission) (Box 8, Folder 283)
- Ripon Society (Box 8, Folder 284)
- Robinson, Jackie (Box 8, Folder 285)
- Rockefeller, Abby (Box 8, Folder 286)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Biography) (Box 8, Folder 287)
- NAR Campaign Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 288)
- NAR Vice Presidential Confirmation (Box 8, Folder 289)
- NAR Vice Presidential Confirmation (Box 8, Folder 290)
- Rockefeller Credo (Box 8, Folder 291)
- Rockefeller/Einstein (Box 8, Folder 292)
- Rockefeller Finances (Box 8, Folder 293)
- NAR: Foreign (Box 8, Folder 294)
- Rockefeller Inaugural Address, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 295)
- Rockefeller Interviews (Box 8, Folder 296)
- Rockefeller Records (Box 8, Folder 297)
- Rockefeller, Nelson A.: source material (Box 8, Folder 298)
- Romney, George (Box 8, Folder 299)
- Ronan, William (Box 8, Folder 300)
- Rule 22 (Box 8, Folder 301)
- Rumsfeld, Donald (Box 8, Folder 302)
- Russia (Box 8, Folder 303)
- Sadat, Anwar (Box 8, Folder 304)
- Salary Articles (Box 8, Folder 305)
- Salary Articles (Box 8, Folder 306)
- SALT (Strategic Arms Limitation Treaty) (Box 8, Folder 307)
- Sample Speeches (Box 8, Folder 308)
- School Speeches (Box 8, Folder 309)
- Science (Box 8, Folder 310)
- Science (Box 8, Folder 311)
- Scottish Americans (Box 8, Folder 312)
- Scott Commission (Box 8, Folder 313)
- Scott, Hugh (Box 8, Folder 314)
- Seidman, William L. (Box 8, Folder 315)
- Senate (Box 8, Folder 316)
- Shafer, Raymond (Box 8, Folder 317)
- Singapore (Box 8, Folder 318)
- Smith, Alfred E. (Box 9, Folder 319)
- Social Security (Box 9, Folder 320)
- Solid Wastes (Box 9, Folder 321)
- Southern Speeches (Box 9, Folder 322)
- Space (Box 9, Folder 323)
- Spain (Box 9, Folder 324)
- Special Prosecutor (Nadjari) (Box 9, Folder 325)
- Speeches (Box 9, Folder 326)
- Speeches, Big 11 (Box 9, Folder 327)
- Speeches, General Information (Box 9, Folder 328)
- Speeches, Questionnaire (Box 9, Folder 329)
- Speech Topics (Box 9, Folder 330)
- State Fair (Box 9, Folder 331)
- State of the Union 1976 (Box 9, Folder 332)
- State of the Union (Box 9, Folder 333)
- STATUS, Federal Statistical Magazine (Box 9, Folder 334)
- Stewart Airport (Box 9, Folder 335)
- Strip Mining (Box 9, Folder 336)
- Student (Campus Disorders) (Box 9, Folder 337)
- SUNY (State University of New York) (Box 9, Folder 338)
- Swearing-In (Box 9, Folder 339)
- Swedish Americans (Box 9, Folder 340)
- Swiss Americans (Box 9, Folder 341)
- Synthetic Fuels (Box 9, Folder 342)
- Tax Cut 1975 (Box 9, Folder 343)
- Taxes (Box 9, Folder 344)
- Transportation Bond Issue, General, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 345)
- Transportation Bond Issue, Speeches/Releases, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 346)
- Television (Box 9, Folder 347)
- Third Party (Box 9, Folder 348)
- Transition (Box 9, Folder 349)
- Transportation (Box 9, Folder 350)
- Transportation Bond Issue 1971 (Box 9, Folder 351)
- Transportation Bond Issue 1973 (Box 9, Folder 352)
- Truman, Harry S. (Box 9, Folder 353)
- Turkey (Box 9, Folder 354)
- Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 9, Folder 355)
- Typewriter Sample (Box 9, Folder 356)
- United Nations (Box 9, Folder 357)
- Urban Development Corporation (Box 9, Folder 358)
- Urban Problems (Box 9, Folder 359)
- Vandenberg, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 360)
- Veneman, John G. (Box 9, Folder 361)
- Venereal Disease (Box 9, Folder 362)
- Vetoes (Box 9, Folder 363)
- Viet-Nam (Box 9, Folder 364)
- Volunteers (Box 10, Folder 365)
- Voting (Box 10, Folder 366)
- Wallace, George (Box 10, Folder 367)
- Washington, George (Box 10, Folder 368)
- Watergate (Box 10, Folder 369)
- Water Pollution (Box 10, Folder 370)
- Water Pollution Control Commission (Box 10, Folder 371)
- Water Quality Commission (Box 10, Folder 372)
- Welfare (Box 10, Folder 373)
- Welfare Inspector General (Box 10, Folder 374)
- Westchester County (Box 10, Folder 375)
- Whitman, Ann (Box 10, Folder 376)
- Wilkins, Roy (Box 10, Folder 377)
- Williamsburg (Box 10, Folder 378)
- Women (Box 10, Folder 379)
- World Bank (Box 10, Folder 380)
- World Trade Center (Box 10, Folder 381)
- Youth (Box 10, Folder 382)
- September 23-25, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  Washington, DC; Beginning of Hearings before Senate Committee on Rules and Administration; 72 page document issued on history of family, family business, NAR chronology.
- September 23-25, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 384)
- October 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  Provo, Utah, Brigham Young University; Message from President Ford; praise for Brigham Young University, confirmation hearings.
- October 2, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  San Francisco, CA; 15th Annual Conference of Editors and Publishers; message from President Ford, freedom of information, confirmation hearings.
- October 7, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  New York, Cooper Union; Great Hall Forum Program; Commission on Critical Choices for Americans.
- October 8, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  Warrenton, VA; 6th Annual Statement In Medicine Award Dinner; award to Dr. C. Rollins Hanlon.
- October 16, 1974 (canceled) (Box 10, Folder 389)
  Foreign Policy Association Luncheon.
- October 25, 1974 (canceled) (Box 10, Folder 390)
  North Tarrytown, NY, Dedication, Phelps Memorial Hospital.
- November 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  Washington, DC; Re-opening of Hearings, Senate Rules Committee.
- November 13, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  Washington, DC; Committee on Rules and Administration.
- November 21, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  Washington, DC; Opening of House Judiciary Committee Confirmation Hearing.
- November 24, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 394)
  House Judiciary Committee Statement.
- December 3, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  Washington, DC; Luncheon with Freshman Republican Congressmen.
- December 5, 1974 (Empty folder) (Box 10, Folder 396)
  Washington, DC; Second Appearance, House Judiciary Committee.
- December 19, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In as Vice President in Senate Chamber.
- January 10, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  Washington, DC; Toast and Luncheon for the Sultan of Oman; toasts.
- January 13, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  Washington, DC; Briefing, Central Intelligence Agency; CIA Activities in the United States.
- January 16, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  Washington, DC; Briefing, Presidential Appointees; Ford.
- January 16, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  Washington, DC; Briefing, Governors & Mayors; local government.
- January 21, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  Washington, DC; American Trucking Association, Outstanding Driver of the Year; traffic safety.
- January 22, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  Washington, DC; GOP Congressional Campaign Committee Reception; Ford, honor to work with Ford.
- January 23, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In Ceremony, Nuclear Regulatory Commissioners; nuclear energy.
- January 23, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  Chicago, IL; National Business Leadership conference sponsored by Junior Achievement; economy, administration's programs.
- January 24, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 406)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In of Marjorie Lynch, Deputy Administrator of the Bicentennial Administration; Bicentennial.
- January 24, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 407)
  Washington, DC; Bicentennial.
- January 28, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 408)
  Washington, DC; Washington Press Club Interview; miscellaneous humorous questions and answers.
- January 28, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 409)
  Washington, DC; World Wildlife Fund, Getty Prize for Conservation; conservation, environment.
- January 29, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 410)
  Milburn, NJ; GOP Fund Raising Dinner; energy & economy.
- January 31, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In, President's Panel on Biomedical Research; health.
- January 31, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  Washington, DC; Dinner given by Prime Minister and Mrs. Wilson; foreign affairs, relationship of United States and Britain.
- February 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 413)
  Washington, DC; United States Travel Service Conference; tourism.
- February 5, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 414)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with Pine Crest Students; history.
- February 6, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 415)
  Washington, DC; Prime Minister Bhutto dinner; toast.
- February 13, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 416)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Dinner, Honoring Vice President; Ford, admiration of Ford's leadership.
- February 14, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 417)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Governors Club Dinner; governors.
- February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 418)
  Washington, DC; National Governor's Conference; local government, government programs.
- February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 419)
  Washington, DC; United States Chamber of Commerce, Breakfast; energy.
- February 19, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 420)
  Washington, DC; Pan American Union, Reception for Felipe Benavides; testimonial.
- February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 421)
  Washington, DC; Republican Governors' Breakfast; republican Party and Domestic Council.
- February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 422)
  Washington, DC; Grocery Manufacturers of America; miscellaneous.
- February 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 423)
  Washington, DC; Black Enterprise Achievement Awards; African-Americans.
- February 25, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 424)
  Washington, DC; National Bicentennial Commission.
- February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 425)
  Washington, DC; SOS and Chowder and Marching Society Breakfast; Domestic Council, energy, economy.
- February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 426)
  Detroit, MI; Society of Automotive Engineers; energy.
- February 26, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 427)
  Washington, DC; South Carolina Young Republicans; Republican Party.
- February 27, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 428)
  Arthur S. Flemming Awards; government and private sector.
- March 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 429)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with Consumers Leaders; consumers.
- March 4, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 430)
  Washington, DC; National Conference of Christians and Jews, Brotherhood Award presented to George Meany; miscellaneous.
- March 7, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 431)
  Washington, DC; Republican Leadership Conference; Republican Party.
- March 21, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 432)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with Coal Industry; energy.
- March 22, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 433)
  Washington, DC; Meeting and Gridiron Dinner; political humor, politics.
- March 25, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 434)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with Agency Directors of Equal Employment; employment.
- March 25, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 435)